{
    "id": "172ad05b678241a3916df1b395e2e0de",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Please give me a ………………… of paper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "peace",
                "piece",
                "peas"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b34225e21ab24542ab59d7d4878f6965"
        },
        {
            "question": "How much is the railway ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fair",
                "fare"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b78ca820a89545f1927850281de0984e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane has got very …………………. looks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "plane",
                "plain",
                "plan"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1b894f5b2314b3b9408ab686192f46d"
        },
        {
            "question": "As he had no shirt, the sun burnt his ………………… . skin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bare",
                "bear"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76fbbe2490c04a05830439bab6444c00"
        },
        {
            "question": "I really want to …………………. some weight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "loss",
                "loose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5b1bcd756f5422f86f47002bacca2db"
        },
        {
            "question": "An oil lamp needs a ………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weak",
                "week",
                "wick"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "858851ff32a6421a980182fa37b03a0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "My little brother is very …………………… so we don’t let him touch anything …………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "irresponsable breakable",
                "irresponsible breakable",
                "irresponsible breakible"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e3652d1c12c491aa2c1ce520854c764"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ………………….. looks like a big rabbit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hare",
                "hair",
                "heir"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ab0f58715ad4f4791c7071891b12bb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was unusually ………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "quiet"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0845865397484fdebd074f893ddbee25"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… . going to the market.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "We're",
                "Were",
                "Where"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0caf6d0b8d7f4265be1465d3a8deea35"
        }
    ]
}